# Project co Ordinator (Engineering & CRM sales)

# Summary

Dynamic and detailed-oriented professional with a comprehensive experience of 6.8 years as Engineering graduate in Civil Engineering. Team player with excellent Analytical, Communication and Interpersonal skills. Assists senior managers with accomplishing demanding targets by encouraging staff and coordinating resources. Methodical and well-organized in optimizing coverage to meet operational demands.

# Skill Highlights

- SAP MM (S4 HANA)
- SAP CRM
- Budgeting/Cost control

- Optimization
- 59
- MS-Office

# Experience

#### Senior executive - 04/2019 to 04/2020 Brigade group, Mysore

- Track customer interactions
- Keep contact information up to date
- Builds workflows for sharing information between marketing automation and CRM
- Creating sale orders using SAP CRM
- Attending customer complaints once the sale order is done
- Interacting with customers from the date of booking till registration process
- Payments follow up with Accounts (Accounts receivable)
- Creating reports on Ageing
- Creating cash flow reports
- Creating statement of accounts to customers
- Collecting site in progress reports form the project engineers and convey the same to customers
- Interaction with Bankers to process the Loans faster to the customers.
- Interacting with customer care Engineer for snags completion before handing over to customers
- Co ordinating with both advocates and customers during registration process
- Clearing final statement of account's and handing over sale order to customers

### Engineer-Projects - 01/2017 to 04/2019 Brigade group, Mysore

- Requirements Planning.
- Purchasing.
- Inventory Planning and Control.
- Ascertaining and Maintaining the Flow and Supply of Materials.
- Quality Materials Control of Materials.
- Departmental Efficiency. improvement projects and their execution

• Involving in 5S Audit

#### Senior Engineer - 09/2014 to 01/2017 Brigade group, Mysore

- Help to form and adhere to company quality standards.
- Testing products or systems.
- Frequently visit construction or worksites to inspect and analyze quality.
- Provide feedback to construction workers.
- Help to turn feedback into actionable points.
- Maintain documentation on product quality.
- Provide reports to Construction Project Managers.

### Trainee engineer - 08/2013 to 09/2014 Brigade group, Mysore

- Completing all tasks set by the supervisor and assisting wherever possible.
- Traveling to different sites and gaining practical experience in new work zones.
- Working closely with staff to foster professional values and build good relationships.
- Observing health and safety guidelines at all times.
- Attending meetings and workshops.
- Submitting to all forms of evaluation during the traineeship.

### Education

#### Bachelor of Engineering in Civil engineering

Visveswaraya technological university, Belgaum

August 2009 – July 2013

#### Professional achievements

- Involved in completing Brigade symphony residential project at Mysuru
- Involved in completing Grand Mercure commercial project Mysuru

### Languages known

- Kannada
- English
- Hindi